Maksym Ivaniuk

TRAINEE FRONT-END
DEVELOPER

SKILLS

HTML
CSS / SCSS / SASS
JavaScript
AJAX
CSS Box Model
Flex Box
Cross Browser CSS
Responsive Web Design
BEM
Bootstrap
Git
Photoshop / Figma

Ukrainian (native)
English (Intermediate)
Polish (Intermediate)
Russian (native)

CONTACT

+380669875164 m.ivaniuk97@gmail.com Ivano-Frankivsk





ABOUT ME

About 1 years ago I was interested in Front-End development and I started to study it using FreeCodeCamp, MDN, HTML Academy simulators, webinars and YouTube videos. In September 2020, I decided to take courses at the Beetroot Academy in order to systematize the acquired and gain new knowledge, experience, mentoring and code review. At the moment, I am studying working with Git and going through the basics of JavaScript again in Udemy courses, improving HTML/CSS code and JS skills on Codewars and my pet projects. Also improove my knowlege of english. Soon I plan to start learning JS framework React, Gulp / Webpack task manager. I appreciate the friendly team and responsibility. I can quickly adapt, search information and learn quickly. I get unreal pleasure from WEB developing. Especially when everything works as it should and benefits the user.

Link to my <u>Github</u>.
Links to my pet - projects(clickable):

<u>Monticello</u>

<u>Travel More</u>

<u>Photographer Portfolio</u>

<u>Calorie Meter</u>

<u>Music Player App</u>

EXPERIENCE

Sept2020 - Febr2021 Junior Front End Developer May2021 - Nov2021 IT Projects

EDUCATION

IVANO-FRANKIVSK NATIONAL MEDICAL UNIVERSITY 09.2013 - 06.2018 | Dentist

BEETROOT ACADEMY

09.2020 - 03.2021 | Junior Front-End Developer